BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15)
1956-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/015
10.5 cubic feet
10.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833679
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 06, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2017
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements - United States.; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives
5833679
- Code no.2116: Weyenberg Shoe Manufacturing Company and Boot and Shoe Worker's Union Locals 170, 379,651, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Code no.2117: Fulton County Glove Manufacturers, Inc. and Consolidated Glove Cutters and Shavers Union Local 1714, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Code no.2367: Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co. and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 222, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Code no.2367: Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co. and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 222, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Code no.2548: Alloy Works of Union Carbide Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 3-89, 1974- 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code no.2646: Dayton Malleable Iron Company, G.H.R. Foundry Division and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America Local 765, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Code no.2669: Kast Metals Corporation, Mid-Continent Steel Casting Division and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Local 333, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code no.3211: Nordberg, Rexnord Inc. Division and United Steel Workers of America Local 1173, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Code no.3213: Teledyne Wisconsin Motor and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 283, 1974- 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code no.3243: Eaton Corporation, Industrial Truck Division and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1717, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code no.3266: ATF-Davidson Company and United Steel Workers of America Local 3654, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code no.3266: Whitin Casting Company and United Steel Workers of America Local 3654, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Code no.3277: SKF Industries, Inc. and United Steel Workers of America Local 2898, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Code no.3318: Dresser Industries, Inc., Waukesha Engine Division and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 10, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Code no.3351: Sperry Rand Corporation, Vickers Division and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 171, 1970-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code no.3378: Caterpillar Tractor Co. and International Association of Machinists Locals 115,284, 1971-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Code no.3384: National Cash Register Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 1067, 1970- 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Code no.3392: Fedders Corporation and Stove, Furnace and Allied Appliance Workers International Union Local 105, 1971-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Code no.3685: Western Electric Company, Inc. and International Brotherhood of electrical Workers Local 1806, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Code no.3750: Western Electric Company, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1470, 1971-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Code no.3764: Euclid Lamp Plant of General Electric Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1377, 1970- 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Code no.3775: Circle F Industries and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1273, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Code no.3789: General Electric Company, Battery Business Department and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2156, 1973- 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Code no.3790: Franklin Electric Co. and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 1000, 1970- 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Code no.3795: A.O. Smith Corporation, Electric Motor Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1977, 1970- 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Code no.4000: ACF Industries, Inc., Carter Carburetor Division and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 819, 1962-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Code no.4063: Curtiss-Wright Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, 669, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Code no.4412: Robertshaw Controls Company, Fulton Sylphon Division and United Steelworkers of America Local 5431, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Code no.4418: GAF Corporation and International Chemical Workers Union Local 306, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Code no.4420: General Time Corporation, Westclox division and United Steelworkers of America Local 12573, 1969-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Code no.4424: Johnson and Johnson and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1437, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Code no.4434: Spartus Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Local 664, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Code no.4615: Mattel and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers Locals 458, 766, 1970-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Code no.4623: Bally Manufacturing Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 713, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Code no.6021: Narragansett Electric Company and Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, Inc. Locals 310,314, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Code no.6021: New England Power Service Company and Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, Inc. Locals 310,314, 1973- 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Code no.6091: Kansas City Power and Light Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1464, 1969-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Code no.6324: Meat Packing Companies of New York and Provision Salesmen and Distributors Union Local 627, 1972-1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Code no.6529: Jordan Marsh Company, Boston, Mass. and United Food and Commercial Workers Local 1445, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Code no.6542: Korvettes Department Stores and Department Store Employees Union Local 21, 1962-1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Code no.6734: Kosher Meat Markets of Greater New York and Hebrew Butcher Workers Union Local 234, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Code no.6749: Dallas Division of the Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 368, 1970-1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Code no.264: Stokely-Van Camp, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America Locals 56,563,662, 1976-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Code no.319: Schenley Distillers, Inc. and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union Locals 6,28,38, 1972- 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Code no.340: Meat Drivers' Working Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 710, 1968-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Code no.342: N/A and Ice Cream, Frozen Custard Industry Employees, Drivers, Vendors and Allied Workers Union Local 717, 1973- 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Code no.364: Morton Frozen Foods and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 29, 1971-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Code no.382: Stokely-Van Camp, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 487, 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Code no.389: Lingerie Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc. and Intimate Apparel Workers' Union Local 62-32, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Code no.394: Del Monte Corporation, Northwest Division and Fruit and Vegetable Packers and Warehousemen Union Local 760, 1973- 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Code no.401: Anheuser-Busch, Inc.- St. Louis, Missouri and Brewery and Soft Drink Workers Conference Local 6, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Code no.511: Jno. H. Swisher and Son, Inc. and Cigar Makers' International Union of America Locals 86,119, 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Code no.855: Men's and Boy's Shirt and Liesurewear Association and Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code no.866: Merit Clothing, Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1973- 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code no.1003: Potlatch Corporation and International Woodworkers of America Local 5-484, 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Code no.1032: Intercraft Industries Corporation and Picture Frame and Moulding Workers' Union Local 18-B, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Code no.1114: Kirsch Company and Kirsch Company Local Union 797, 1971-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Code no.1228: Riegel Paper Corporation and United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 1712, 1971-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Code no.1247: Crown Zellerbach and United Paperworkers International Union, 1970-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Code no.1258: Inland Container Corporation and United Paperworkers International Union Locals 31-S,114-S,1046-S,4658-S,737-S,954-S,1029-S, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Code no.1280: Armstrong Co. and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers Local 461, 1967-1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Code no.1402: Boston Daily Newspapers and Boston Typographical Union 13, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Code no.1424: Graphic Arts Employers of South California and Graphic Arts International Union Locals 63, 63A,63B, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Code no.1639: Rohm and Haas Company and United Class and Ceramic Workers of North America Local 88, 1971-1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Code no.1653: Sherwin-Williams Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-268, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Code no.1804: Continental Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 5-857, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Code no.1924: Formica Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Local 757, 1971-1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Code no.6852: Fernandes Super Markets, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers Local 4A, 1974-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Code no.6902: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and Northern Santa Clara County and International Association of Machinists Local 1414, 1974-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Code no.6911: Shoe Retailers League, Inc. and Retail Shoe Employees Union 1268, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Code no.7119: Santa Barbara/Ventura Restaurant Association and Bartenders and Culinary Workers Union Local 498, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code no.7141: Independent Restaurants, Bowling Establishments, Taverns, Cocktail Lounges and Cafeterias and Hotel, Motel, Restaurant, Food Service and Bartenders Local 74, 1971-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Code no.7507: Chicago Residential Hotel Association and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union Locals 593,25,88,278,450,484, Chicago Joint Executive Board, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Code no.7527: Independent Hotels of St. Louis and Hotel, Motel, Restaurant, Food Service and Bartenders Local 74, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Code no.7960: Shubert Theatrical Interests and Theatrical Protective Union Local 1, 1967-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Code no.7960: League of New York Theatres and Theatrical Protective Union Local 1, 1967-1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Code no.7983: Animated Film Producers Association and Motion Picture Screen Cartoonists Local 839, 1973-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Code no.7990: N.E.C.A., Western New York State Chapter and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 41, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Code no.8458: Ohio Valley Construction Employers, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Steel Valley District Council, 1964-1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Code no.8476: Contractor's Association of Westchester, Putnam and Dutchess Counties, Inc. and Laborers International Union of North America Local 60, 1970-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Code no.8548: Contracting Plasterers' Association and Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association Local 60, 1956- 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Code no.8567: Building Trades Employers Association of Central NY and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 12, 1974-1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Code no.8611: South California Glass Management Association and Glaziers, Glassworkers and Architectural Metal Workers Local 636, 1970- 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Code no.8663: Allied Construction Industries of Delaware, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 626, 1973- 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Code no.8695: Associated General Contractors of Minnesota and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Locals 221,346,160,487, Joint Council 32, 1969-1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Code no.8708: Mechanical Contractors, District of Columbia Association, Inc. and Plumbers Local Union No. 5, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Code no.8741: Detroit Mason Contractors Association and Laborers' International Union of North America Locals 334-1076, 1966- 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Code no.8758: Steel Erectors Association of Baltimore and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers Local 16, 1974-1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Code no.8814: Associated Sheet Metal, Roof and Insulating Contractors of CT and NY and Sheet Metal Workers Local Union 40, 1971- 1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Code no.8820: National Electrical Contractors Association, Inc., Louisville Chapter and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 369, 1967-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Code no.591579: Peabody Coal Company and United Mine Workers of America, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Code no.591580: Uniform Manufacturers' Exchange Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, New York Joint Board, 1965- 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Code no.591592: National Twist Drill and Tool Company and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement workers of America Local 771, 1959-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Code no.591605: Mead Corporation and Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union Local 527, 1974-1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Code no.591609: RM Friction Materials Company and United Textile Workers of America Local 2590, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Code no.591612: Gimbel Brothers and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1407, 1976-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Code no.591621: Aggregates and Concrete Association of Northern California, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Locals 216,287,315, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Code no.591626: A.S. Abell Company and Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Code no.591644: Georgia-Pacific Corporation and International Woodworkers of America Local 3-469, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Code no.591652: United Can Company and Cannery Warehousemen, Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers Union Local 768, 1974- 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Code no.591662: Knitwear Employers Association, Inc. and Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Code no.591663: Cooper Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers Local 207, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Code no.591684: Cities Service Company, Pinto Valley Operations and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 310, 1974- 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Code no.591695: Central Hardware Co. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 655, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Code no.591703: Bullard Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 7528, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Code no.591733: Construction Employers Association of Central Kentucky, Inc. and Kentucky Laborers' District Council Locals 189,586, 1977- 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Code no.591769: Seattle Department Stores Association and Office Workers' Division of Driver Sales and Warehouse Local 117, 1978- 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Code no.591773: Cleveland Automobile Dealers Association and International Association of Machinists Local 1363 of District 54, 1979- 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Code no.591251: Gas Service Company and United Steelworkers of America Locals 12329, 12561, 13417, 14224, 14228, 15162, 1969- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Code no.591274: Bridgeport Brass Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 4266, 1965-1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Code no.591305: Boston Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 387, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Code no.591310: American Can Company, Easton Plant and Forks Plastic Plant and United Paperworkers International Union Local 412, 1973- 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Code no.591343: Park-Ohio Industries, Inc. and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 91, 1968- 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Code no.591352: Yellow Cab Company of Pittsburgh and Taxicab Drivers Union Local 128, 1965-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Code no.591356: Building Owners and Managers of Oakland and Service Employees International Union Local 18, 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Code no.591374: Grand Union Company and United Food and Commercial Workers Local 371, 1971-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Code no.591384: Cunningham Drug Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 876, 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Code no.591429: Breweries of Detroit, Michigan and Brewery Workers' Local Unions 181, 1038, 1968-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Code no.591443: Golden Operations, Inc. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Local 86, 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Code no.591448: ITT Rayonier, Inc. and United Paperworkers International Union Local 787, 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Code no.591450: Stanley G. Flagg and Co. and United Steelworkers of America Local 2326, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Code no.591453: S.D. Warren Company and United Paperworkers International Union Local 1015, 1972-1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Code no.591454: National Electrical Contractors' Association, Northern California Chapter, Alameda County Section and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 595, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Code no.591455: Keebler Company and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America Local 253, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Code no.591457: Heil-Quaker Corporation and Stove, Furnace, and Allied Appliance Workers International Union Local 14, 1974- 1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Code no.591476: Building Trades Employers Association of Central NY and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 12, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Code no.591495: Eaton Corporation, Industrial Truck Division and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 433, 1967-1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Code no.591523: Pharmaseal Laboratories and United Metaltronics and Hospital Supply Employees Local 955, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Code no.591525: Philadelphia Newspapers, Inc. and Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Code no.591528: GTE Automatic Electric Inc. and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 28, 1973-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Code no.591545: Amoco Production Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 4-16, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Code no.591550: Todd Shipyards Corporation and Galveston Metal Trades Council, 1969-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Code no.591554: New York Telephone Employees' Association and Upstate Telephone Employees' Association, 1960-1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Code no.591556: Sunshine Biscuits, Inc. and Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers Union Local 50, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Code no.591561: Garlock, Inc. and International Association of Machinists, District 6, Lodge 588, 1961-1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Code no.591562: Life Savers, Inc. and Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers Union Local 697, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 28)